罗斯  这个慧星什么时候会来
Ross, whers this comet thing start?
理论上来说  七百万年前
Well, technically, it started 7 billion years ago.
好  我不讲课  好吗
Okay. Fine, I'll stop. No teaching, okay?
我们只欣赏美丽的流光划过天空
We'll just watch the pretty light streaking across the sky.
好
Okay?
它的正式名字是巴布斯坦王 好 好
Whose official name is Bapstein-King. Okay! Okay!
在那儿  你看
There it is. Oh, look at that!
大自然多神奇啊
Isn't Mother Nature amazing?
那是飞机
That's a plane.
1700袋花生能飞那么高
Well, all right, 1700 bags of peanuts flying that high...
也挺神奇的
...that's pretty amazing too.
我在想飞机上能不能看到我家
I wonder if you can see my apartment from up here.
不能  看不到
No, you can't.
-什么  -我不知道
- What? - I don't know.
看看这些星星
Man, look at all those stars.
无边无际的空间  遐思无限对吧
Infinite space. It really makes you wonder, doesn't it?
-你知道什么还让你遐思无限吗  -什么
- Know what else makes you wonder - What?
看看那个妞的胸部
Check out the rack on that chick.
我们已经在外面两个小时了
We've been out here for two hours...
还没看到那愚蠢的彗星  我们能走了吗
...and we haven't seen any stupid comets. Can we go now?
我是说  钱德勒冻死了
I mean, Chandler's getting chilly.
不  我没有
No, I'm not.
那你为什么穿着莫妮卡的外套
Then why are you wearing Monica's jacket?
因为好看
Because it's flattering!
走吧  莫妮卡  走吧  莫妮卡
Come on, Monica. Come on, Monica.
我们也要走了
We're gonna take off too.
-租了电影看  -我也想看电影
- Rented a movie. - I won't say no to a movie.
菲比  其实我们想独处
Oh, Pheebs, we just actually wanted to be alone.
-带我一起走哦  -好
- Get me out of here. - Oh, okay.
-嘿  罗斯  -怎么了
- Hey, Ross. - What?
-快来看  -那是慧星吗
- Check this out. - Is it the comet?
不  这有只被焦油黏住的虫
No. Look, there's a bug stuck in tar right here.
我简直不能相信
I can't believe...
我带你来看巴布斯坦王慧星
I bring you here to see the Bapstein-King comet...
大自然最壮观的现象之一
...one of nature's most spectacular phenomena...
而你只关心被焦油黏住的虫和一个女人
...and all you care about are bugs stuck in tar and some woman.
你知道  有两个女人  老兄
You know, there's two women, dude.
在哪里
Show me where.
好  在那里
Okay. Right up here.
乔伊  我们拿来顶住门的管子呢
Joey, where's the pipe that was holding the door open?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道
Yeah, I do.
-乔伊  -怎么了  别看着我
- Joey! - What? Hey, don't look at me!
是你非要上来
You are the one who wanted to come up here
看什么愚蠢的汉堡王彗星的好吗
and look for some stupid Burger King comet.
那是巴布斯坦王慧星  好吗
It's called the Bapstein-King comet, okay?
巴布斯坦是一位很受尊敬的太空人
Hey, Bapstein was a very well-respected astronomer from...
不
No!
-莫妮卡  -她在睡觉
- Monica. - She's sleeping.
我知道  就问一个简单的问题
I know. Just a quick question.
《慧星撞地球》是哪部《世界末日》又是哪部
Which one was Deep lmpact and which one was Armageddon?
《慧星撞地球》是有罗伯特·杜瓦那部
Deep lmpact was the one with Robert Duvall.
如果你再叫醒我就会知道什么叫做世界末日了
Armageddon is what's going to happen to you if you wake me up.
抱歉  我就是睡不着
Sorry, I just can't sleep.
你看的那本书在哪里
Where's that book you're reading
有两个女人在溜冰
with two women who are ice-skating...
还带着上面有花的帽子
...and wearing those hats with the flowers on it.
每次一看到封面  我就
Because every time I look at that cover, I'm like...
在客厅  那儿有灯
It's in the living room, where there's also a light...
而且没有人会踢你小腿
...and no one will kick you in the shin.
什么
What?
拜托请别是太空飞船  拜托请别是太空飞船
Please don't be a spaceship. Please don't be a spaceship.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
你怎么可能还在哗  我不是把你卸下来了吗
How could you be beeping? I just disconnected you!
我把电池取出来了  你怎么  别打断我
I took out your battery! How can...? Don't interrupt me!
瑞秋  莫妮卡
Rachel! Monica!
真是的
Come on!
真受不了
I can't believe this!
我大概知道我们应该怎么下去了
All right, well, I guess we know what we have to do to get down.
我想我们也别无选择了
Yeah, I guess we don't have a choice.
救救我们  请救救我们
Help us! Please help us!
我们被困在屋顶  下不去
We're stuck up on the roof, and we can't get down!
罗斯
Ross.
我是说我们可以顺着消防梯下去
I was thinking we'd just go down the fire escape.
我知道  我还没说完
I know. I wasn't finished.
但是不用担心
But don't worry!
我们可以顺着消防梯下去
We're gonna go down the fire escape!
抱歉  我想热点牛奶
I'm sorry, I thought I'd make some warm milk
来帮助睡眠
and it would help me sleep.
用炒瓢热
With a wok?
我以为你要看我那本无聊的书来帮助睡眠
Thought you were gonna read my boring book to put you to sleep?
那书还挺有趣的
It got interesting.
可恶的欧普拉
Damn you, Oprah!
我来替你热牛奶  反正我已经起来了
Here, let me make the milk. I'm up anyway.
既然我们已经起来了 你知道可以做什么吗
You know what we could do now that we're up?
我们可以秉烛夜谈
We could just talk to each other all night long.
像我们第一次约会时那样  会很有趣的
Like we did when we were first going out. It'd be fun.
-听起来是很有意思  -对
- Okay, that does sound fun. - Yeah.
二姐去世的时候你是不是很难过
So how bummed were you when the second sister died, huh?
二姐去世了
The second sister dies?!
没有
No.
没有  我是在说我看的那本书
No, I was talking about the book I was reading.
《阿契漫画合集》里的二姐死了
The second sister dies in Archie and Jughead Double Digest?
对
That's correct.
想回卧室吗  会更舒服一点
Want to go in the bedroom? It's a little more comfortable.
-当然  -好
- Sure. - Okay.
等一下  你有没有把合约寄去米兰
Oh, wait, did you send those contracts to Milan?
你觉得这对话性感吗
If this is your idea of sexy talk...
我说认真的呢  记得我给你的合约吗
No, seriously, you know that contract I gave to you?
你有没有拿明日到达的快递寄送出去
Did you overnight them?
什么合约
What contracts?
拜托告诉我这是你另一个我搞不懂的笑话
Please tell me this is just one of your jokes you do that I don't get.
还有其他你搞不懂的笑话呢
Like what?
像是你把电话放在裤子里
Like the thing when you put the phone in your pants?
泰格  我认真的  这不好笑
Tag, I'm serious. This isn't funny.
合约必须今天发出去
Those contracts had to go out today.
瑞秋很抱歉  但是你没给过我合约
Rach, I'm sorry. You didn't give me any contracts.
我有  我还贴了一张即时贴  写着
Yes, I did. I put a little Post-it on it that said:
"今天一定要寄出"
"Must go out today,"
还在"今天"下面划了三道
And I underlined "Today" Three times.
我还在角落画了一颗心
Then I put a little heart in the corner
因为我不想太颐指气使
because I didn't wanna seem too bossy.
你没有给我
You never gave them to me.
如果我们到办公室去
If we went to the office,
你会看到合约就在你的办公桌上
you would see those contracts sitting on your desk.
不  我会看到你很窘迫
No, I'd see you looking embarrassed
因为合约就不在我办公桌上
because they are not on my desk.
也许我会因为你用裤裆接电话
Maybe I'd look embarrassed
所以才看起来很窘迫
because you're talking on the phone with your crotch.
你想现在去办公室吗
You want to go to the office now?
很晚了  我们别去办公室了
Come on, it's late. We're not going down to the office.
我理解  我也不想被证明自己是错的
Yeah, I understand. I wouldn't want to be proved wrong either.
好  拿上你的外套
All right, get your coat!
你什么时候解开的  不错啊
Oh! When did you unook this? Nice work!
下不去了  卡住了
It won't go down any further. It's stuck.
我们只有跳下去
We're just gonna have to jump.
我们一定要确定着陆在
Now, we're gonna have to make sure to land...
那块冰的右边  好吗
...to the right of that patch of ice, okay?
不要撞到旁边的垃圾桶
Not hit the dumpster on the other side.
试着避开中间那棕红色的奇怪东西
And try to avoid that weird brownish-red stuff in the middle.
当你到下面以后
So when you get down there...
你去屋顶开门让我进去
...you go up to the roof and you let me in.
-慢着  必须得我跳  -没事啦
- Wait a minute. I have to do it? - You'll be fine.
就像蹦极一样
It'll be just like bungee jumping, you know?
但你就是不会弹上来罢了
But instead of bouncing back up, you won't.
要是我的头撞到水泥地了呢
Well, what if I smack my head on the concrete?
乔伊  我不想骗你  是有这个可能的
Well, I'm not gonna lie to you, Joey. It's a possibility.
我不知道  我们扔硬币决定谁去
I don't know. Tell you what, let's flip to see who does it.
-到空中再说你要哪一面  -好
- You call it in the air, all right? - Oh, all right.
-你能看见是哪一面吗  -看不到
- Can you see what it is? - No.
-你小心一点  -罗斯 不要这样
- Okay. Well, you be careful. - No, Ross, stop it.
我不跳
I'm not jumping.
我明天还有试镜
Look, I have an audition tomorrow,
如果摔断腿就不能去了
and I can't go if I break my leg.
我也不跳  我可是有儿子的人
Well, I'm not jumping. I have a son.
我死了他就没爸了
He won't have a father if I die.
看来我们平手
So it looks like we're even.
好  这条线
Okay, so this wire...
接着这条线  插到这儿
...is connected to this wire, which plugs into here.
想让哔声停止  我只要
Okay, so to get the beeping to stop, all I have to do...
做得好  菲比
Well done, Pheebs.
你要我怎么样
What do you want from me?!
你的牛奶来了  你想谈什么
Here's your milk. What do you wanna talk about?
什么  什么  什么
What? What? What?
你睡着了吗甜心  对不起  给
Oh, were you sleeping, sweetie? I'm sorry. Here.
随便看
Okay. Feel free to look...
不过我告诉你  合约没在这张桌上
...but I'm telling you, those contracts are not on this desk.
你怎么可能知道  你看看有多乱泰格
How could you possibly know? Look at this mess, Tag.
我告诉过你了  要有条理一点
This is what I'm talking about. You have to be more organized.
有报纸  有杂志
You've got newspapers, you've got magazines, you... Oh!
这小妞是谁
And who's this chippy?
对你来说太幼稚一点  随便啦
A little young for you, Tag, but whatever.
是我妹
That's my sister.
真的  牙套好可爱
Really? Very cute braces.
无所谓啦  关键在于  开始找吧
Anyway, you know what? The point is, Tag, start looking...
你会在你桌上找到那合约
...because you're gonna find those contracts on your desk.
你觉得你是什么时候给我的  上午还是下午
So when do you imagine you gave them to me? Morning or afternoon?
下午  塞纳先生午饭后来我这里了一趟
In the afternoon. Mr. Zelner came into my office after lunch...
他把合约放在我桌上  然后我贴了即时贴
...he put them on my desk, and then I put a Post-it on it...
写着
...that said:
"今天一定要寄出"
"Must go out today."
请你继续找  好吗
So you just keep looking in there, all right?
不在这里
They're not here.
奇怪
Puzzler.
真奇怪
Bit of a puzzle.
你去影印室找一找
Why don't you check the copy room.
也许你落在那了
Maybe you left the contracts in there.
-我怎么可能放在那儿  -我不知道
- How could I have left them there? - I don't know.
你的私处怎么可能打电话
How can your genitals make phone calls?
这并非完美世界  去找找行吗
Okay? It's not a perfect world. Just go, please?
-行  -谢谢
- Fine. - Thank you.
喂
Hello?
我还是不懂
I still don't get it.
你还醒着吗
You still awake?
是啊  你呢
Yeah. You?
你知道说话的是我吧
You do know that was me that just said that, right?
嗨
Hey.
既然我们都醒着
As long as we're both up...
怎样
Yeah?
我希望你不是想要打扫客厅
I hope you're not thinking about cleaning the living room.
我饿死了  晚饭的时候我都吃了些什么啊
Man, I'm starving. What the hell was I thinking at dinner?
"要汤还是沙拉"  当然永远都是两者都要
"Do you want soup or salad?" Both, always order both.
我看了半天  我想没人在家
You know, I'm looking, and I don't think anyone's home here.
我们应该打破玻璃
I say we just break the window...
爬进去
...crawl through...
过会再解释
...and you know, explain later.
-没人在家  -应该没人
- No one's home? - I don't think so.
有人吗
Hello?
所以你进去之后
So when you get in there...
你我该在这里分手了
Okay. This is where you and I part ways.
吵死人的贱货
Noisy bitch!
怎么  你在干什么
Oh, what? What are you doing?
你知道刚刚发生什么事吗
Do you know what just happened?
我们做爱  然后我们睡着了
Yeah. We had sex, and then we fell asleep.
不  我们做了一半
No. We were in the middle of sex...
然后你睡着了
...and you fell asleep.
不不  才不是
No. No, that's not true.
这是最棒的一次
No, best time ever.
改变了我的世界观
Yeah. You rock my world.
-莫妮卡  -怎么了
- Monica? - What?
我刚用了我最好的招数  你却错过了
I was giving you some of my best moves, and you missed it.
快起来  我们好好做一次
So please wake up so we can do it right.
好  我准备好了
Okay. Okay. I'm ready.
-大哥快来吧  -好
- Come on, big fella. - Okay.
-来点精彩的  -好
- Give me the good stuff. - Yeah.
别啊  别睡啊
No, no, no. Don't fall asleep.
我去给你煮点咖啡
Okay, I'm going to make you some coffee.
我应该不会
Well, I probably won't spill
把咖啡渣粉得满厨房都是
coffee grounds all over the kitchen floor.
我起来了  起来了
Okay, I'm up. I'm up.
嘿  咖啡来了
Hi. I got you some coffee to...
你找到东西了没
So you got anything for me?
-还是没有  -我的天
- Still no luck. - Oh, my God.
你检查过整个桌子和所有的抽屉吗
You checked your entire desk and all the drawers?
-要我再找一次  -请你再找一次
- Want me to check again? - I wish you would.
没有在这里
Well, no, it's not in there.
那个抽屉呢
How about that drawer?
不在  会在你办公室吗
Well, it's not out here. Any chance it could be in your office?
我不知道
I don't know.
我找找看
I mean, let me check.
有吗
Any luck?
请进来说话
See you in my office for a minute?
你找到了
You found them!
我不会沾沾自喜
I'm not even gonna gloat.
我只是很欣慰这件事情终于结束
I'm just really relieved that this whole thing is over...
是你放在我桌上的
You put these on my desk.
-我没有  -是吗
- I did not. - Oh, really?
所以它是从你最下面的抽屉溜出来
They slid out of your bottom drawer...
爬过地板   跳到我桌上来的吗
...crawled across the floor, then jumped onto my desk?
你怎么知道它在我最下面的抽屉里
How did you know they were in my bottom drawer?
你真是让我欲火焚身啊
I am so hot for you right now.
我的天 你怎么回来的
Oh, my God! How did you get back here?
菲比·布菲
Phoebe Buffay?
火警
Fire Alarm?
火警先生  有什么我能帮你的吗
Oh, hi, Officer Fireman. Can I help you?
我们在垃圾桶里发现了你的烟雾探测器
We found your fire alarm in the trash.
-不是我的  -是你的
- That's not mine. - Yes, it is.
-你怎么知道  -下次你丢掉探测器时
- How do you know? - Next time you dump a fire alarm in the trash...
别用一张上面写着
...don't use a blanket that says,
"菲比·布菲财物  非莫妮卡所有"的毯子
"Property of Phoebe Buffay, not Monica."
你有搜查证吗
Do you have a search warrant?
这里还是美国
Because the last time I checked, this was still America.
请把它装回去  拆除它是违法的
Please reattach it. It's illegal to disconnect them.
好吧  但拜托请告诉我怎么能让它停止叫唤
Fine. But please, God, tell me how to stop it from going off?
塑料盖子下面有个重设的钮  按一下
Press the reset button under the plastic cap.
有重设按钮  谢谢  谢谢
There's a reset button? Oh, thank you. Thank you.
还有重设按钮呢
Oh. There's a reset button?
天啊
My God!
我怎么没看见
Why didn't I see that?
重设按钮  重设按钮
Reset button. Reset button.
重设按钮在哪里哦  在这儿
Where is there a reset button? Oh, here it is! Oh!
-你抓好了吗  -好了
- Okay, you have a good grip? - Yeah.
我要顺着你向下爬了
I'm gonna start to climb down you now.
-好  你动作快点  -好
- All right, just hurry up. - Okay.
我应该面向你爬下来  我们脸对脸
Now, should I climb down your front so we're face to face...
还是顺着你的背趴下来
...or should I climb down your back so we're...
屁股对脸
...butt to face?
-脸对脸  -我喜欢脸对脸
- Face to face. - I like face to face.
-好  我来了  -好
- Okay, here I come. - All right.
填啊  你有多重啊  罗斯
Oh, my... How much do you weigh, Ross?
我拒绝回答
I prefer not to answer.
节日的幸福还留在我身上
I'm still carrying a little holiday weight.
我们说脸对脸的时候
When we talked about face to face...
我们没想清楚这个流程
...I don't think we thought it all the way through.
-你想怎样  -赶紧顺着我向下
- What do you want me to do? - Just shimmy down me and drop.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
也许我应该挂着  你顺着我爬
You know, maybe I should hang, and you should climb down me.
-是吗  -我们应该聊聊这个
- Yeah? - Maybe we should talk about that for a little while!
-看着离地还是很远  -不远了  跳吧
- It still looks pretty far. - It's not that far. Just drop.
别催我
Do not rush me!
我裤子快掉了
You should know my pants are starting to come down,
我又没穿内裤
and I'm not wearing any underwear.
我的脚踝  我的脚踝
My ankle! I really hurt my ankle!
我觉得我脚踝扭了  25美分硬币
I think I twisted it when... A quarter!
确实是你最好的招数啊
That really was some of your best work.
告诉过你了
I told you.
简直让人无法置信
I can't believe it.
在我请病假之前只剩2小时了
I've only got two hours until I call in sick for work.
我7分钟之后要起床
I have to be up in seven minutes.
你不会相信的
Well, you're not gonna believe this,
但是既然你还有7分钟
but if you have seven minutes...
真的吗
Really?
你要吗
You want to?
你负责吸尘器  我负责给家具打蜡
You get the vacuum cleaner. I'll get the furniture polish.